It's summer, so it's a great time to be outdoors.
现在是夏天，所以是户外活动的好时机。
One way of letting your hair down and enjoying the fresh air is to attend a music festival, where you can enjoy seeing your favourite musicians perform.
放松心情、享受新鲜空气的一种方式是参加音乐节，在那里你可以欣赏你最喜欢的音乐家的表演。
But it's not just about the music – there are other activities to enjoy.
但这不仅仅是关于音乐——还可以参加其他活动。
And of course, it's a chance to spend time with your friends.
当然，这也是一个与朋友共度时光的机会。
People have always enjoyed communal gatherings – even in prehistoric times, people would come together, have feasts and celebrate – and part of the occasion involved playing or listening to music.
人们一直喜欢公共聚会——即使在史前时代，人们也会聚在一起，设宴和庆祝——而活动的一部分就涉及演奏或聆听音乐。
So, music festivals are nothing new.
所以，音乐节并不是什么新鲜事。
But they have evolved, and in recent times, one of the most famous music festivals was Woodstock in the USA in 1969.
但它们在进化，在近代，最著名的音乐节之一是1969年在美国举行的伍德斯托克音乐节。
This al fresco event was one of the largest ever to be staged and promised 'three days of peace and music'.
这场户外活动是有史以来举办的最大规模活动之一，承诺"三天和平与音乐"。
It attracted a large 'hippie' crowd.
它吸引了大量的嬉皮士人群。
And in 1970, the Glastonbury festival began on a farm in the UK and now spreads across 900 acres of land.
1970年，格拉斯顿伯里音乐节在英国的一个农场开始，现在扩展到占地900英亩的土地。
It has become a highlight in a festival goers' music calendar, attracting major headline acts and large crowds who camp out for the weekend.
它已成为节日观众音乐日历上的一个亮点，吸引了重量级表演嘉宾和大量露营度过周末的人群。
Although they often have to endure rain and mud!
尽管他们常常要忍受雨水和泥泞！
Other festivals that have become huge include the Danube Island Festival in Austria, the Mawazine Festival in Morocco, the Isle of Wight Festival in the UK, and Coachella in the USA – a music and arts festival that features every genre of music.
其他规模变得巨大的音乐节包括奥地利的多瑙河岛节、摩洛哥的Mawazine音乐节、英国怀特岛音乐节以及美国的科切拉音乐艺术节——这是一个以各种音乐流派为特色的音乐艺术节。
But from the mainstream to the niche, there seems to be a festival for everyone taking place around the world.
但从主流到小众，世界各地似乎有一个适合每个人的节日。
And festivals have become big business too.
音乐节也已成为大生意。
According to research by Festicket, in 2018 the music festival industry was worth $3bn globally, and it has continued to grow.
根据Festicket的研究，2018年全球音乐节产业价值为30亿美元，并且持续增长。
Many events have become commercialised.
许多活动已经变得商业化。
Ticket prices are high and corporations and social media influencers cash in on festival themes.
票价很高，企业和社交媒体网红们利用节日主题获利。
Despite all of this, for many hedonistic young people, attending a festival has become a rite of passage and a shared experience that can't be missed.
尽管如此，对于许多享乐主义的年轻人来说，参加音乐节已经成为一种成人礼和不容错过的共同经历。
Writing for BBC Culture, Arwa Haider says "for any generation, they're unlike any other place on earth: a site liberated from everyday rules, where we might bond with strangers and stumble across new sounds and sensations."
阿娃·海德尔为BBC文化撰稿时说："对任何一代人来说，它们都不同于地球上的任何其他地方：一个从日常规则中解放出来的场所，在那里我们可能与陌生人建立联系，并偶遇新的声音和感觉。"